Finding Aid for Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated.
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: Veterans Memorial Library,undated (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: Vocational Education,undated (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: Volunteering,undated (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: Warriner Hall and Mall,undated (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: WCML-TV,undated (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: WCMU-FM,undated (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: Wellness Center,undated (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: Women’s Study Program,undated (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Mixed Photographs, N, S-Y: Youth Discovery,undated (Box 86, Folder 42)
  - Small Headshots, A-F,undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Small Headshots, F-K,undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Small Headshots, L-Pa,undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Small Headshots, Pe-S,undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Small Headshots, T-Z / Miscellaneous,undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Football,undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Women’s Baseball,undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Track,undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Volleyball,undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Soccer,undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Chip Center,undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Chipettes, Outdated,undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Chippewa Club,undated (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Theater,undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Sport Collection and Public Broadcasting, Slides, outdated, Photographs: Public Broadcasting,undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Headshots, A-F, outdated,undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Headshots, G-M outdated,undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Headshots, Me-T outdated,undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Headshots, W-Z outdated,undated (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, E-F: English,undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, E-F: Enrollment,undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - News Releases, E-F: Enrollment Student Services,undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, E-F: Extended Learning,undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, E-F: External Relations,undated (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, E-F: Faculty Association,undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, E-F: Faculty Center for Academic Success,undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, E-F: Faculty Center for Innovative Teaching,undated (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, E-F: Faculty Contractual,undated (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, E-F: Feature Tip,undated (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, E-F: Finance,undated (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - News Releases, E-F: FAS,undated (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, E-F: Financial Aid,undated (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, E-F: Flood of ’86,undated (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, E-F: Foreign Language,undated (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, E-F: Free Speech,undated (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, G-H: Gay and Lesbian Programs,undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, G-H: Geography,undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - News Releases, G-H: Gerontology,undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, G-H: Gov. [Governor] Engler,undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, G-H: Govt. [Government] Relations,undated (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, G-H: Graduate Studies,undated (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, G-H: GRIP (Graduation, Retention Improvement Program),undated (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, G-H: Grants,undated (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, G-H: Grants and Contracts,undated (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, G-H: Graphics,undated (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, G-H: GLISS (Great Lakes Institute for Sustainable Systems),undated (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - News Releases, G-H: Health Education, Health Science,undated (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, G-H: Health Professions,undated (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, G-H: Health Services,undated (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, G-H: Higher Education,undated (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, G-H: Higher Education 2,undated (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, G-H: Higher Education Week,undated (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, G-H: History Deportment,undated (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, G-H: CMU, General History,undated (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - News Releases, G-H: Homecoming,undated (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - News Releases, G-H: Hometowns,undated (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - News Releases, G-H: Hometowns 2,undated (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - News Releases, M: Mac Users Group,undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, M: Management,undated (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - News Releases, M: Maps,undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, M: Marketing Hospital Service,undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, M: Math,undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, M: Math/ Science Teaching Center,undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, M: McNair Program,undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, M: Media Relations,undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, M: Medical Schools,undated (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Associations of Governing Boards,undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Campus Compact,undated (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Geographic Alliance,undated (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Institute for Adult Learning,undated (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Melody,undated (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Molecular Institute,undated (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Press Association,undated (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, M: Michigan Schools in the Middle,undated (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, M: Midland Programs,undated (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, M: Military Science,undated (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - News Releases, M: Office of Minority Affairs,undated (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - News Releases, M: Miscellanies,undated (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - News Releases, M: MSU News Bulletin,undated (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - News Releases, M: Mount Pleasant,undated (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - News Releases, M: Multicultural Programming Center,undated (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - News Releases, M: Multigene,undated (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - News Releases, M: Music File 3,undated (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - News Releases, M: Music File 4,undated (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - News Releases, M-P: Music File 2,undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, M-P: Music File 1,undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - News Releases, M-P: Native American Program,undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, M-P: Neithercut Woodlands,undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, M-P: Network for Women,undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, M-P: News Sources,undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, M-P: Nontraditional Student Services,undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, M-P: Odyssey of the Mind,undated (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, M-P: Office of Research,undated (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, M-P: Office of Student Success,undated (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, M-P: On the Fly,undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - News Releases, M-P: OTD (Opportunity for Talent Development,undated (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, M-P: Orchesis,undated (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, M-P: Park Library,undated (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, M-P: Parking,undated (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, M-P: Personnel Services-Faculty,undated (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, M-P: Personnel Services,undated (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, M-P: Personnel Services-Sttaff,undated (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, M-P: Philosophy,undated (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - News Releases, M-P: Physical Education and Sports,undated (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - News Releases, M-P: Physical Plant,undated (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - News Releases, M-P: Physical Therapy,undated (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - News Releases, M-P: Physician’s Assistant Program,undated (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - News Releases, M-P: Physics,undated (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - News Releases, M-P: Placement,undated (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - News Releases, M-P: Plachta,undated (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - News Releases, M-P: Political Science,undated (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - News Releases, M-P: Politics-State and Local,undated (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - News Releases, M-P: Politics-National,undated (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - News Releases, M-P: [Gerald L.] Poor Museum,undated (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - News Releases, H-L: Hometowns,undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, H-L: Hometown,undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - News Releases, H-L: Honors Program,undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, H-L: Housing,undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, H-L: HEV [Health Environmental Studies],undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, H-L: HSBS, College of [Humanities and Social and Behavior Sciences],undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, H-L: Humanities Institute,undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, H-L: IET,undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, H-L: Information Technology,undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, H-L: Instructional Materials Center,undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, H-L: Institutional Research,undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - News Releases, H-L: International Center for Applied Ethics,undated (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, H-L: International Program,undated (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, H-L: IPR Program [Integrative Public Relations],undated (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, H-L: Job Training Center,undated (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, H-L: Journalism,undated (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, H-L: LaBelle Center,undated (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, H-L: Lem Tucker Scholarship,undated (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, H-L: Leadership Institute,undated (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Finance, Insurance, and Real Estate,undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Food Services,undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Footbal,undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Football 2,undated (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Football 3,undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Foreign Language,undated (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Geology Department,undated (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Golf,undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Greeks,undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Gymnastics,undated (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Health Services – Foust,undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Historical,undated (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: History Department,undated (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Homecoming,undated (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Honors,undated (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Housing,undated (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Colored Slides, F-I: Human Environmental Studies,undated (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: IET,undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: IPCD,undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: MMT (Unidentified acronymn, people in lab coats with various equipment),undated (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Management Department,undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Marching Band,undated (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Marketing and Hospitality Services,undated (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Math Department,undated (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Medical Technology,undated (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Minority Affairs,undated (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Mount Pleasant Community,undated (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Multi-Cultural Center,undated (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Colored Slides, I-M: Museum of Cultural and Natural History,undated (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: MacDonagh -Dumler, Etta,undated (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: MacGillivray, Maureen,undated (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mackey, Marcia,undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Macleod, David I.,undated (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Macleod, Elizabeth,undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Macleod, Jon H.,undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Marian B. Macleod,undated (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Madison, Lynn,undated (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Magnell, Kenneth R.,undated (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Magnuson, Michaelina,undated (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mahon, Andrew,undated (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Maksimowicz, Michelle Lee,undated (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Malone Beach, Eileen,undated (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Manns, Cynthia,undated (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Manville, David,undated (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Marcum, Tanya,undated (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mark, Dianne,undated (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Marron, Maria,undated (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Martin, Darrell Irwin,undated (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Martin, Jay,undated (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Martin, Sue Ann,undated (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mascolo-David, Alexandra,undated (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mason, Emmett,undated (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mason, John,undated (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Masterson, Tom,undated (Box 104, Folder 25)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mathews, David,undated (Box 104, Folder 26)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mathis, Paul C.,undated (Box 104, Folder 27)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mathur, Mary E. Fleming,undated (Box 104, Folder 28)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Matouka, Robert,undated (Box 104, Folder 29)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Matty, David,undated (Box 104, Folder 30)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: May, Hope,undated (Box 104, Folder 31)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McAuliffe, John C.,undated (Box 104, Folder 32)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McBane, Donald,undated (Box 104, Folder 33)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mcbrayer, Deborah,undated (Box 104, Folder 34)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McCann, Connie,undated (Box 104, Folder 35)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McCarthy, John L.,undated (Box 104, Folder 36)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McDermott, William,undated (Box 104, Folder 37)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McDonald, James,undated (Box 104, Folder 38)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McGinnis, Amy,undated (Box 104, Folder 39)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McGrath, John,undated (Box 104, Folder 40)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McLean, Athena,undated (Box 104, Folder 41)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: McNaught, Scott,undated (Box 104, Folder 42)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Meadows, Elizabeth,undated (Box 104, Folder 43)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Meiss, Guy,undated (Box 104, Folder 44)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Meixner, John,undated (Box 104, Folder 45)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mellinger, Axel,undated (Box 104, Folder 46)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Joan Memering,undated (Box 104, Folder 47)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Memering, Willard D.,undated (Box 104, Folder 48)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Merrill, William,undated (Box 104, Folder 49)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Merritt, Barbara Anne,undated (Box 104, Folder 50)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mesler, Gary L.,undated (Box 104, Folder 51)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Messick, Frederic M.,undated (Box 104, Folder 52)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Metcalf, Douglas,undated (Box 104, Folder 53)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Messick, Frederic M.,undated (Box 104, Folder 54)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Metcalf, Douglas,undated (Box 104, Folder 55)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Meyer, John C.,undated (Box 104, Folder 56)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miele, Tony,undated (Box 104, Folder 57)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mika, Harry,undated (Box 104, Folder 58)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Barbara Fisher Miles,undated (Box 104, Folder 59)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miles, Susan Goodrich,undated (Box 104, Folder 60)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miles, Thomas J.,undated (Box 104, Folder 61)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miles, William,undated (Box 104, Folder 62)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miller, Gray M.,undated (Box 104, Folder 63)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miller, Kent,undated (Box 104, Folder 64)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miller, Kevin,undated (Box 104, Folder 65)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miller, Mary Ann,undated (Box 104, Folder 66)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miller, Robert H.,undated (Box 104, Folder 67)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Miller, William A.,undated (Box 104, Folder 68)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mills, Maureen W.,undated (Box 104, Folder 69)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mills, Robert C.,undated (Box 104, Folder 70)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Minelli, Mark,undated (Box 104, Folder 71)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Scott Minick,undated (Box 104, Folder 72)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Minkel, Thomas A.,undated (Box 104, Folder 73)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Minnis, Marybeth,undated (Box 104, Folder 74)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Minyard, Charles,undated (Box 104, Folder 75)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mioduszewski, Leo,undated (Box 104, Folder 76)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mishra, Nandita,undated (Box 104, Folder 77)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mitchell, John B.,undated (Box 104, Folder 78)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mitchell, Regina,undated (Box 104, Folder 79)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Moffit, Gisela,undated (Box 104, Folder 80)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Moffit, Thompson C.,undated (Box 104, Folder 81)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mohanty, Dillip,undated (Box 104, Folder 82)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Monahan, John,undated (Box 104, Folder 83)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Monahan, Nina,undated (Box 104, Folder 84)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Monfils, Anna,undated (Box 104, Folder 85)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Monroe, James S.,undated (Box 104, Folder 86)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Montoye, Mary J.,undated (Box 104, Folder 87)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: James Moody,undated (Box 104, Folder 88)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Moore, Colleen,undated (Box 104, Folder 89)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Moore, Thomas,undated (Box 104, Folder 90)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morgan, Denise Lois,undated (Box 104, Folder 91)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morgan, Sharon,undated (Box 104, Folder 92)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morris, Gregory,undated (Box 104, Folder 93)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morris, Kenneth T.,undated (Box 104, Folder 94)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morrison, Richard,undated (Box 104, Folder 95)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morrisroe, Julia,undated (Box 104, Folder 96)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morton, Cornez,undated (Box 104, Folder 97)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Morrow, Earl,undated (Box 104, Folder 98)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Moscardelli, Deborah,undated (Box 104, Folder 99)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mostrom, Elizabeth,undated (Box 104, Folder 100)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Motlagh, Hugh,undated (Box 104, Folder 101)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Moursi, Mahmoud A.,undated (Box 104, Folder 102)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mower, Neil,undated (Box 104, Folder 103)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mowrey, Merlyn,undated (Box 104, Folder 104)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mrochinski, Linda,undated (Box 104, Folder 105)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mueller, Anja,undated (Box 104, Folder 106)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Mull, Ian,undated (Box 104, Folder 107)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Murchison, Pamela W.,undated (Box 104, Folder 108)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Murphy, David,undated (Box 104, Folder 109)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Murphy, Kelly,undated (Box 104, Folder 110)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Murphy, Lawrence,undated (Box 104, Folder 111)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Murray, Lorrie,undated (Box 104, Folder 112)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Masial, Gloria,undated (Box 104, Folder 113)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Myers, David,undated (Box 104, Folder 114)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Nance, Douglas W.,undated (Box 104, Folder 115)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Naomi, Leora,undated (Box 104, Folder 116)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Narayan, Sivaram,undated (Box 104, Folder 117)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Nash-Robertson, Nina,undated (Box 104, Folder 118)
  - News Releases Faculty / staff, Mac-Plachta: Nasser, Abdul,undated (Box 104, Folder 119)